iprecio.com 2018-04-23

# Privacy Policy

### www.iprecio.com by Primetech Corporation, Tokyo, Japan; Privacy Policy

Primetech Corporation owner of www.iprecio.com ("Primetech") respects user privacy on our web site. Primetech abides by a strict compliance program for collecting or using personal data protection, and this compliance program is continually being improved to ensure the protection of any and all private information. This privacy policy is designed to provide specific information about the privacy and data collection practices for this site: www.iprecio.com 

**Disclaimer**

This Privacy Policy is applicable to Japan, where the server for this website resides.

 **Identifying Information**

In general, you can visit this website without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to support our relationship with you, such as to enable you to sign up for a mailing list, or follow up with you. Primetech asks for identifying information when you:

  1. Want to contact Primetech to ask for information.
  2. Participate in a sweepstakes, or other promotional offer.
  3. Register to receive mailings, or e-mail notification about press releases & newsletters.

In these instances, Primetech will ask for your name, e-mail address, or other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, it will be clear to you that you are submitting this type of information. In addition, if you choose to receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings as described in the Opting-Out section below.

 **Communications from you**

When you e-mail or write to us, you may provide us with your name, contact details and other Personal information as part of your message.

 **What Primetech will do with your information**

If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by Primetech and is used by Primetech only to support your relationship with us. Primetech will/may share relevant personal information with our authorized distributor in your country of enquiry/address to fulfil any of the purposes above and will be retained by our distributor only to support your relationship with them.

 **What others may do with your information**

Primetech does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through the Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time Primetech may use third party agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for Primetech (such as a database management service) but only in accordance with this stated privacy policy. And Primetech requires certain safeguards in place by any vendors with access to personal data collected by Primetech, including a written commitment to keep the information confidential and to only use the data to carry out the services for Primetech. In addition, Primetech may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PC users Windows 7 and y percent Windows 10 users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about any of our users.

 **Opting Out**

If you have registered for the press release and/or newsletter mailing list, and would like to opt-out, contact us at [iprecio@primetech.co.jp](mailto:iprecio@primetech.co.jp?subject=Unsubscribe%20Request) with subject line unsubscribe with relevant personal information so that we will be able to confirm your requests correctly. 

**Collecting aggregate data and cookies**

Like many web sites, Primetech collects non-personal data about how the site is being viewed. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. The Site includes analysis features which enable Primetech to capture aggregate data about how the site is used, such as the amount of total traffic, the number of page views or the number of unique visitors. This feature does not capture personal identifying information about any visitors to the Site. Primetech reviews this data and uses it only for internal purposes of assessing and for managing the Site. Primetech uses cookies on our site to make the user experience better. A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a website to your computer's hard drive. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer.

 **Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to integrate and optimize web pages where appropriate. “Google Analytics” is a service offered by Google Inc. “Google” that generates detailed statistics about a website's traffic and traffic sources and measures conversions and sales. Google Analytics uses “cookies” stored on your computer to help analyze how users use our website.

The information generated by the cookies about your use of our website, including your IP address, will be anonymized by use of the appropriate settings (“_anonymizelp()” function or equivalent) and transmitted to Google servers in the United States. For more information on how IP anonymization works please see <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2763052>.

On behalf of us, Google will use the information generated by the cookies for the purpose of evaluating the use of our website, compiling reports on website activity providing us with these reports for analytical purposes.

Google may transfer this information to third parties in case of a statutory obligation or if a third party processes data on behalf of Google. Under no circumstances, Google will combine or associate your IP address with other data stored at Google.

You may prevent or stop the installation and storage of cookies by you browser settings by downloading and installing the free Opt-out Browser Add-on available at <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. We inform you that in such case you will not be able to wholly use all functions of our website.

By using our website you consent to the processing of any personal data Google will collect on you in the way and for the purpose as described above. 

**Children’s privacy protection**

Primetech is aware of the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 16. The vast majority of the material on the Site is not intended for children and is not targeted to children under the age of 16. Primetech does not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will remove this information from our database.

 **Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

To ensure the security and confidentiality of Personal Data that we collect online, we use data networks protected, inter alia, by industry standard firewall and password protection. In the course of handling your Personal Data, we take measures reasonably designed to protect that information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

 **Third party links**

This website does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have their own privacy and data collection practices. Please note that once you click on one of these sites, you leave the Primetech Site and Primetech has no control or responsibility for the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements at those sites as you visit them.

 **Changes to this policy**

Primetech may from time to time revise its privacy policy. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.

 **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, you can contact us at [iprecio@primetech.co.jp](mailto:iprecio@primetech.co.jp).

March 14, 2018.
